♪  It seems today
that all you see  ♪
♪  Is violence in movies
and sex on TV  ♪
♪  But where are those
good old-fashioned values  ♪
♪  On which we used to rely?  ♪
♪  Lucky there's a family guy  ♪
♪  Lucky there's a man
who positively can do  ♪
♪  All the things that make us  ♪
♪  Laugh and cry  ♪
♪  He's... a...
Fam... ily... Guy!  ♪
Aw, man, I've been dying
to see Maniac Pope 2.
The first one
was awesome.
Is this one
of those theaters
where they bring your beef stew
right to your seat?
What? That's
not a thing.
Sure is.
Don't get mad at me 'cause
you don't know nothing fancy.
I feel like I'm
being watched.
Of course
you are, silly.
The Lord is always
watching us.
May the sword
be with you.
And also with you!
Geez, this movie sucks.
I know,
it's terrible.
Excuse me,
who had the stroganoff
with the roasted
potatoes?
Right here.
Thank you for seeing me,
Your Excellency.
Of course.
What did you say your
name was, my child?
Lucy.
You've been "Lucified."
That was awful.
I know, they just redid
all the same stuff
from the first
Maniac Pope.
Yeah, like in the first
Maniac Pope,
he says to Bruce,
"You've been Brucified."
Like, that's
smart, right?
That's a smart line.
But he did the same thing
twice in this movie.
Once to Lucy and once earlier
when he found that wild goose.
It's just
bad writing.
Yeah, I mean, we could write
a better horror movie than t Th.
Really? You
think we could?
Absolutely, I'm as creative as
the first spider to spin a web.
Hey, you know how
we always dreamed
about having a house
that comes out of our butts?
Uh, what?
Eh?
Yeah.
Butt-house.
I found your cigarettes.
That's all I'm gonna say.
Morning, everybody.
And the crisis
continues.
What, these?
Come on.
Last thing I want
is attention.
It's just that when you've
read as many books as I have,
it-it takes a toll,
you know?
You sure it's not
from watching
too much close-up
porn on your phone?
You know,
I wouldn't be surprised
if they have that now.
Brian, what do you
want for breakfast?
Uh, hold on.
What do I want?
You're so full of it.
You don't need
those things.
Wait, who said that?
Oh, Stewie.
You are just horrible.
You're even worse
than those people
who take dumps
in the shower.
What?
W-Why are you cutting to me?
What did somebody say?
Whatever they said I do,
I don't do.
All right, I got a
horror movie idea.
It's called
Cereal Killer.
A serial killer who only
kills people who eat cereal.
Wait, what... what if God
is a serial killer?
He lowers the average lifespan
of humans to 65,
but there are many exceptions
based on genetics and diet.
That's stupid-- I ain't never
heard of somebody lived to 65.
Look, I think the problem is
this is a bar.
We can't get
inspired here.
We have to go someplace
scary, you know?
To put us in the mood.
I got it: the old Quahog Asylum.
What?!
We can't go there.
That place has been
abandoned for years.
And they say it's haunted
by a ghost with a hook-hand.
That's why it's
the perfect place.
If we want to write
a scary movie,
we need to do it
somewhere scary.
Well, I guess
we could try it.
We have sort of just been
spinning our wheels here.
No offense, Joe.
I guess
Cleveland's right.
So far, this has been
a bigger waste of time
than an acceptance speech
at the Asperger's Awards.
I'd like to thank
everyone I've ever met,
in the order that I met them,
last name first,
and if anyone interrupts me,
I'll have to start over.
♪   ♪
This place
is terrible.
Are you kidding?
It's the perfect place
to write a horror movie.
All right, well,
I got an idea.
You know, I like
them horror movies
where you got a couple
of teenagers getting busy
in their car
at Makeout Point,
but there's a killer
on the loose.
He Stacy, what do you say
we go all the way tonight?
And then I unload
on the sun visors.
Is that all
you ever think about?
And besides, Richie,
aren't you worried
about what the man on the radio
is saying right now?
Another dead teenage couple
was found at Makeout Point,
clawed beyond recognition.
You see?
There's a dangerous
creature out there.
Oh, what, you mean the
big, rabid, slobbery cat
what's been scratching
people to death?
I don't believe
it exists, Stacy.
Now, help me get the right
angle and lower the visor.
Richie,
did you hear that?
Will you calm down?
We're the only
ones out here...
Rrrawwwr!
Oh, my God!
Wait, you were the guy
and the cat?
And what's with
that visor stuff?
Did Richie achieve
release?
Okay, of the three
of you,
Cleveland's the only one
who gets it.
That's an awful idea.
Well, I got one.
We should write one
of them zombie movies
where a guy wakes up in a
comfortable cotton hospital gown
with the back open so there's
a nice breeze on your behind,
and he's like, "This ain't bad."
But then he notices
the hospital's empty.
Nurse, I'm ready
for my sponge bath.
Hmm.
What happened to this place?
Everybody up and gone.
Hmm, that's annoying.
Maybe it's a loose filament.
Nope, that's a busted bulb.
These are all 145s.
I need a 180.
Well, now, maybe I did
need a 145.
There we go.
Damn it, I guess
it's a wiring issue.
That's it?
What the hell? When do
the zombies show up?
That's the thing.
Their shuttle was late.
I-I don't know,
I-I was thinking
we'd write a movie
where something
that's not supposed
to be scary becomes scary.
Like an evil doll.
Yeah, or-or like an
evil bar of soap.
Peter, I don't think
that's such a good id...
Too late.
Oh, yeah, that's nice.
Time to wash my body
with this harmless bar of soap.
Hey, Ambassador Mumbasa,
are you enjoying
that new soap I bought you
from that mysterious Chinese man
whose store was weirdly
not there the next day?
Ambassador Mumbasa?
Oh, my God, Ambassador Mumbasa!
Assistant Ambassador Armstrong?
Everything okay up there
with the bath?
I wonder if everything's okay
up at the old embassy.
All right, maybe coming here
wasn't such a great idea.
Is anybody else getting
a little freaked out
by all these
scary stories?
Yeah, even my
spine is tingling.
You guys, I'm scared.
You remember
that movie, The Blob?
What if the Blob?
Let's get out of here.
Aw, damn it, it's locked!
Oh, my God, somebody
must have locked us in.
We're gonna
die in here!
Sorry, guys,
somebody e-mailed me a video
of a sheep screaming.
It was him.
It was the hook-handed killer.
He locked us in!
All the windows
have bars on 'em.
I think the only way out of here
is through this duct system.
Guys, do the words
"dead by dawn" scrawled
in feces over there
mean we're in trouble?
Did you do it?
I did.
Then no.
Still sticking with
the glasses, huh?
What? Oh, right.
Right,
I have glasses.
They're such a part of me now,
I-I forgot all about 'em.
You're gross.
You know, it's funny,
I-I've gotten an awful
lot of writing done
You're a writer?
I-I like to consider
myself an observer.
You have nice
breasts, for instance.
You want to join me?
Guy with glasses
can't be all bad.
Thanks.
Boy, it's loud
in here, huh?
Wh-When they said "Professor
Griffin," I barely heard them.
That's it, I'm putting
an end to this.
I'm gonna destroy those glasses
if it's the last thing I do.
You should
really check out
the Thanksgiving jazz
CD they sell here.
Where the hell are we?
I heard something.
Is... is someone else here?
Oh, my God,
it's Hook-hand!
He's coming for us!
Damn it, why can't
I get any reception?
Because we're in a basement
in the middle of nowhere.
Besides,
if cell phones worked,
every movie would be
two minutes long.
Like An Affair
to Remember.
♪   ♪
Darling, I was running
to the Empire State Building
to see you,
but I got hit by a car.
No wonder you were late.
I'll be right down.
Are you okay?
I think I may be paralyzed.
I'm sorry, there's nobody here
by that name.
♪   ♪
Wow, Stewie, thanks for
taking me to the spa.
Hey, you deserve
it, buddy.
So just relax, take
your glasses off,
take a nice,
dry sauna--
no glasses in
the sauna--
just leave those
puppies in the locker.
They'll be safe
out here.
Sounds good.
Come on, Chris.
Don't let me down.
Don't worry, Stewie.
Chris!
What are you
doing in here?
I did it.
I locked us in the sauna!
You what?!
Yep, it's all set.
It's turned up high,
and nobody is coming
for the whole weekend.
Boy, you guys sure
look steamed.
This Family Guy joke was
written by Jimmy Sullivan,
age nine, of Decatur, Georgia.
Thanks, Jimmy!
And we'll pass along your
gross request to Mila Kunis.
Those footsteps
are getting closer.
Those aren't footsteps.
It's an old building.
Just relax.
Besides, I can see an exit door
right there.
Where?
Right there.
Behind that guy with the hook--
Everybody run!
Wait a minute.
There's four of us,
and one of him.
Yeah, let's
get him!
Son of a bitch!
Take that!
Die, Hook-hand!
You won't kill us!
Um, Hook-hand's name is Albert,
and he's dressed like a janitor.
I've been...
trying to help you.
I'm the caretaker here.
Wait, you work here?
But you have
a hook hand.
I was a soldier.
I lost my hand
saving six men in Korea.
Oh, God, he's
a war hero.
He's dead.
What have we done?
We killed
an innocent man.
Well, if this doesn't justify
a McFlurry, nothing does.
Oh, my God,
we killed an innocent man.
We-we've got
to report this!
We gotta turn
ourselves in!
No way.
If we do that,
we'll all go to jail.
And I'm a cop.
Do you know what they
do to cops in jail?
Hey, man?
When you were
a cop, did they--
did they let you
use the siren?
Yeah, it's part
of the job.
That's so cool!
Hey, hey, when
you were a cop,
when you were going
to a crime scene,
did you go "chung Chung,"
like Law & Order?
No, that would be
very unprofessional.
All right,
all right.
Oh, hey, check it out,
man, when you were a cop,
did you ever, you know,
use your handcuffs
when you were getting
kinky with your girl?
No, it's city property,
so you're not really
supposed to take those home.
Oh, for sure, for sure.
Oh, hey, by the way,
a bunch of us are gonna kill
you in the shower later.
Okay, so we're all on
the same page, right?
We bury the body,
we never speak
of this again.
Deal. - Got it.
Yup.
Wow, that was exhausting.
Wait a minute, is-is that--
is that his car?
Aw, crap, it's still alive!
It does not feel
like a Wednesday.
Peter, I'm glad
you're up.
I need to talk to you
about something.
I know what you did
last night.
You do?
How could you do
something so heinous?
Last night,
you left your dirty dishes
in the sink.
It's disgusting.
So I did half, and I left
the other half for you.
Ah, forget it.
You'll just do it wrong.
I'll wash 'em myself.
Why don't you just go
in the other room and relax?
I'll call you
when breakfast is ready.
Okay.
Oh, my God, Peter,
come look at the newspaper!
"Janitor dead."
What? No!
Right here.
My college roommate, Jan Itter.
She passed away yesterday.
Are-are we really
doin' this?
'Cause I didn't get, like,
any sleep last night.
What are you
freaking out about?
You didn't even know her.
Yeah, yeah, yeah,
y-you're right, you're right.
You and the guys
killed and buried a man?!
Ah, I knew
you'd find out!
Find out what?
I just got
David Sedaris' new book,
You and the Guys Killed
and Buried a Man.
Okay, I am
really on edge
and this thing we're doin',
I'm not happy about it,
and that's a very odd title
for a humorist's book.
Peter, you're acting
very weird.
Just go in
the other room.
I don't want to go
in the other room,
I want to stay here and
see what you're seeing,
because you're saying
things that I think are
somethin' totally different
than what they are.
Peter, you're gonna
have a heart attack.
I won't say anything,
I'll let you relax.
"They found a body
of a war hero
down by the old asylum!"
Okay, that has to be something.
Oh, sorry, Peter,
I'm just singing along with
this old John Mellencamp song.
♪  They went up there
to write a movie  ♪
♪  Peter, Quagmire,
Cleveland and Joe  ♪
♪  Killed the old janitor
war hero  ♪
♪  Just why, we'll never know  ♪
I don't remember
this one.
Guess it's never been
in a car commercial.
♪  In a truck
that's built Dodge Tough!  ♪
Oh, yeah, no,
I know this one.
Hey, Bri?
Yeah? Aah!
Damn it! Aah!
There's glass in my eye!
Oh! Son of a bitch!
Aah!
Mom says dinner's at 6:00.
She wanted me to tell people,
I don't know why.
Guys, I'm kind of freaking out
about killing that guy.
Anybody else have
a hard time sleeping?
No, but there's an old
John Mellencamp song
you're not gonna
believe.
Wait, w-what's
all this stuff
about you guys
killing someone?
Last night,
at the asylum.
We killed
that war hero.
Whoa, whoa, what?!
You-you really
killed someone?
Holy moly, I don't think
I want to hear this.
Quagmire, you were
there with us.
You're so weird.
Last night, I was
in St. Louis.
I even have
a picture.
See that?
That's yesterday's date
on that newspaper.
On The Quahog Informant?
They sell The Quahog
Informant in St. Louis?
Well, probably, but good
luck with that whole
"you three and not me
killed a guy" thing.
Damn it, that bastard
is bailing on us.
He's a worse accomplice
than Johnny Wind Chimes.
Hey! Shh!
Sorry!
It's my chimes.
I hate to frame you like this,
Quagmire, but I gotta.
I can't go to jail!
They'll razz me good
on account of my belly.
Cleveland?
What are you
doing here?
both doing here?
Joe?
What the hell?
You backstabbers.
What the hell's
going on?
I'll tell you
what's going on.
Cleveland's tryin' to frame me.
He's got my miniature
portraits of cool guys.
Peter, those are baseball cards.
Whatever. He's using it
to frame me for murder!
Well, I'm not
the only one.
Joe's got my Sports Illustrated
football phone.
He was using this
as his main phone.
It is a mess over there.
Look at all
you pathetic people,
bringing stuff
to frame each other.
You're supposed
to be friends.
Hey, that's
my shovel!
Damn right!
That's how smart I am,
I only had to bring one thing!
This way I can dig the hole
and just throw this in!
But once you throw
it in there,
how you gonna get
the dirt back on top?
Give me your shovel!
You're gonna have
to kill me first!
Not with my shovel!
That's brand-new!
Give me back
my rattle-y plastic phone!
♪   ♪
Wait, wait, wait, guys! Guys!
What?
Don't you see?
This!
This is our horror movie!
♪   ♪
It doesn't feel
like a Wednesday.
Boy, that sucked.
Yeah, I guess writing a movie
isn't as easy as Joseph
Gordon-Levitt makes it look.
Hey, at least
we gave it a shot.
I just feel bad
we killed an innocent man.
Well, don't feel too bad.
Look at that!
Oh, my God!
Wow, that's a relief!
We may have actually made
this town a better place.
Yeah, what a monster.
But at least now
he's gone forever.
Thank you for watching "Family Guy" on
www.FOX-fan.ru